Waiting on your post about Donald Trump, the Epstein files, the way in which Black women are under attack, how these HBCUs have lost funding, how people are being snatched off the street without due process, about alligator Alcatraz, about the National Guard being deployed in D.C., about the dismantling of the Department of Education.
I'm out of characters, but there is more that you could be screaming about outside of Kamala's book.
So this type of loud, virulent ignorance is why if you have a passport, you should consider moving.
Because this person might be in your community and might be someone you're actually like depending on.
And they just listed basically like the entire index of my content for the last two years and thought they ate like I'm eating this bread.
And all in the context of defending a person who ran for president that hasn't spoken about any of those things.
If you actually consumed my content, instead of consuming what people say about my content or watching it when it is posted on one of these Black sites that actually promotes Black toxicity, then you would know what I'm really about.
And that everything that you're saying here is what I have literally dedicated my life to discussing on a daily basis.
What you left out is that Kamala Harris, Joseph Biden, and the entire administration are Zionists who not only supported and funded, but committed to continuing a genocide that we are now seeing in its final phase.
And if that is not something that you feel needs to be discussed and addressed, then literally nothing you have to say is of any consequence.
You're damn rude, eh?